Nothing gets real until
DO NOT BE EXPERIENCED
- JOHN KEATS
EVEN IF IT IS
IN THE RIGHT PATH,
YOU WILL BE HELPED IF YOU JUST
BE SITTING THERE.
WILL ROGERS
DREAMS ARE NOT ACCEPTED IN THE
YOUR LOCAL SUPERMARKET
ADAM LOULE, WRITER
FRAUDED WRITER
A DAY TO LOVE
Subpack by DanDee
The.
- Good Morning.
- Good morning Good Morning.
He stayed up all night.
It balked again.
This is disgusting, you need to stop
Eat, or they will still kill you.
Noodles is easy to make, dear,
Inexpensive and addictive.
It is the cigarettes of
Modern writers.
Maybe I should
Start smoking.
IT IS.
Of course, my love.
You should really start smoking.
No need, I wash.
Not alright.
You always wash.
I have to do
My share.
You always look this way.
It's only until I can
A real job.
I wish I could take you to
A decent restaurant.
Well, at least
You know I'm not
With you for your money.
Funny.
Okay, we used to
Laugh more, more.